# LUIS ENRIQUE GUMIEL PARDO

Front end web developer

#### PERSONAL DETAILS

#### **Date of Bird**

July 19th, 1996

#### **Address**

Cota Cota calle 36-A

#### **Phone**

+59168030902

#### Mail

luisegp10@hotmail.com

# Portfolio

https://luis-gumielportfolio.netlify.app/

# **Nationality**

boliviana

### LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/luis-enriquegumiel-pardo-50596b22b

# Languages

Spanish

English

### **Qualities**

- Teamwork
- Creativity
- Empathy
- Leadership
- Passion for learn

## **PROFILE**

I'm a passionate person about programming, who seeks to grow every day and expand his knowledge in web development. I have solid knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.JS and MySQL. In backend I have worked with Node.js to build servers, API requests from the frontend and database with MongoDB. I also have experience working with C# and ASP.NET. I have great skills in communication, teamwork, empathy and creativity to personal growth. Right now I seek to improve myself every day and be a better web developer.

# **EDUCATION**

2002-2014 Colegio San Ignacio de Loyola

Bachelor's degree, Humanities

2015-2021 Universidad Privada Boliviana

Engineer's degree, Computer Systems Engineering

# **EXPERIENCIA LABORAL**

#### IT INTERNSHIP

PROESA - Dic 2020- Jul 2020

Management of SQL databases, Technical support in the company and advice on installation and management of programs.

#### **DIRECT WORK**

PROESA - Jun 2021- Dic 2021

Implementation of a web application for managing vacations, licenses, medical leave and salary loans. Use of the Laravel framework for project development, Jetstream, AdminLTE, Eloquent, MySQL, Bootstrap, Tailwind and Highchart.js

# **COURSES AND CERTIFICATIONS**

#### React: De cero a experto (Hooks y MERN)

#### Feb -2023

The course was based on Hooks and functional components, basic JavaScript review, deepening in hooks, states, props, HOC, API requests, MERN, unit tests, hook tests, customHooks, context, Redux, Material UI, Bootstrap Firebase, Moongose, JWT, Google Sign-In,Fetch, mocks, spys, snapshots, ReactReact Testing Library, JEST and production implementations of real projects.

# <u>Patrones de Diseño en JavaScript y TypeScript</u>

# May -2023

The course includes the following design patterns: Observer, Builder, Singleton .Bridge, Decorator, Strategy and State. Each design pattern included its implementation in JS and in TS. With examples with real cases from day to day and learn to identify when to apply them correctly.